Register of the Commonwealth Club of California records
Hoover Institution Archives
- Program File, 1916-2006 (Boxes 382-605)
  - 1979
    - Dalai Lama (Box-folder 481: 15)
    - Davis, Al (Box-folder 481: 16)
    - Deak, Nicholas (Box-folder 481: 17)
    - Dengler, Dieter (Box-folder 481: 18)
    - Deusche, Alexander (Box-folder 481: 19)
    - Deutch, John (Box-folder 481: 20)
    - Eisdorfer, Carl (Box-folder 481: 21)
    - Elekdag, Sukru (Box-folder 481: 22)
    - Ellsworth, Robert (Box-folder 481: 23)
    - Enthoven, Alain (Box-folder 481: 24)
    - Erdman, Paul (Box-folder 481: 25)
    - Evron, Ephraim (Box-folder 481: 26)
    - Fadiman, Jeff (Box-folder 481: 27)
    - Feinstein, Dianne (Box-folder 481: 28)
    - Field, Mervin D. (Box-folder 481: 29)
    - Fisher, Anthony G. A. (Box-folder 481: 30)
    - Flanagan, Joseph J. (Box-folder 482: 1)
    - Follis, Anne (Box-folder 482: 2)
    - Fonda, Jane (Box-folder 482: 3)
    - Forrester, Eugene (Box-folder 482: 4)
    - Frosch, Robert (Box-folder 482: 5)
    - Ghorra, Edouard (Box-folder 482: 6)
    - Gianturco, Adriana (Box-folder 482: 7)
    - Givens, William L. (Box-folder 482: 8)
    - Goldin, Harrison (Box-folder 482: 9)
    - Goyan, Jere (Box-folder 482: 10)
    - Grade, Lew (Box-folder 482: 11)
    - Gunther, Gerald (Box-folder 482: 12)
    - Haas, Walter (Box-folder 482: 13)
    - Haig, Alexander M. (Box-folder 482: 14)
    - Halbouty, Michel T. (Box-folder 482: 15)
    - Hallett, Carol (Box-folder 482: 16)
    - Hammer, Armand (Box-folder 482: 17)
    - Hanley, John W. (Box-folder 482: 18)
    - Hannon, Stuart L. (Box-folder 482: 19)
    - Harr, Karl C. (Box-folder 482: 20)
    - Hasan, Mohamad Ali Bin (Box-folder 482: 21)
    - Hatch, Orrin (Box-folder 482: 22)
    - Hawley, Philip M. (Box-folder 482: 23)
    - Hayakawa, S. I. (Box-folder 482: 24)
    - Hayden, Tom (Box-folder 482: 25)
    - Hayes, Janet Gray (Box-folder 482: 26)
    - Hayward, Thomas B. (Box-folder 482: 27)
    - Hechinger, Fred M. (Box-folder 482: 28)
    - Henderson, Nicholas (Box-folder 482: 29)
    - Hoadley, Walter (Box-folder 482: 30)
    - Holdren, John P. (Box-folder 482: 31)
    - Hostage, G. Michael (Box-folder 482: 32)
    - Hypmovation, Inc. (Box-folder 482: 33)
    - Jackson, Henry M. (Box-folder 483: 1)
    - Jarvis, Howard (Box-folder 483: 2)
    - Jasinowski, Jerry (Box-folder 483: 3)
    - Jaworski, Leon (Box-folder 483: 4)
    - John Paul II, Pope (Box-folder 483: 5)
    - Jones, Reginald V. (Box-folder 483: 6)
    - Jordan, Hamilton (Box-folder 483: 7)
    - Jordan, Vernon E. (Box-folder 483: 8)
    - Kassebaum, Nancy (Box-folder 483: 9)
    - Kay, Richard B. (Box-folder 483: 10)
    - KCBS forum (Box-folder 483: 11)
    - Kean, John (Box-folder 483: 12)
    - Kemp, Jack F. (Box-folder 483: 13)
    - Kennedy, Edward (Box-folder 483: 14)
    - Kim, Jin Seong (Box-folder 483: 15)
    - King, Llewellyn (Box-folder 483: 16)
    - Klestil, Thomas (Box-folder 483: 17)
    - Koleda, Michael S. (Box-folder 483: 18)
    - Korean ambassador (Box-folder 483: 19)
    - Korn, Lester B. (Box-folder 483: 20)
    - Krueger, Robert (Box-folder 483: 21)
    - Laffer, Arthur (Box-folder 483: 22)
    - Lalonde, Marc (Box-folder 483: 23)
    - Leach, Norman E. (Box-folder 483: 24)
    - Lenczowski, George (Box-folder 483: 25)
    - Le Pelley, Guernsey (Box-folder 483: 26)
    - Levitt, Arthur (Box-folder 483: 27)
    - Li, Victor (Box-folder 483: 28)
    - Literature awards, 48th annual (Box-folder 483: 29)
    - Lowe, Pardee (Box-folder 483: 30)
    - Lyet, Jean Paul (Box-folder 483: 31)
    - McCloskey, Paul N. (Box-folder 483: 32)
    - McClure, James (Box-folder 483: 33)
    - McGarry, Thomas (Box-folder 483: 34)
    - McNamara, Joseph D. (Box-folder 483: 35)
    - Maier, Cornell C. (Box-folder 483: 36)
    - Maksoud, Clovis (Box-folder 483: 37)
    - Marcus, Stanley (Box-folder 484: 1)
    - Margaret, Princess, Countess of Snowdon (Box-folder 484: 2)
    - Marshall, Ray (Box-folder 484: 3)
    - Martinez, Vilma (Box-folder 484: 4)
    - Marusi, Augustine (Box-folder 484: 5)
    - Maynard, Robert (Box-folder 484: 6)
    - Mayoral debate (Diane Feinstein and Quentin Kopp) (Box-folder 484: 7)
    - Metzer, Peter (Box-folder 484: 8)
    - Miller, George (Box-folder 484: 9)
    - Miller, Terry (Box-folder 484: 10)
    - Miller, William G. (Box-folder 484: 11)
    - Mitchelson, Marvin (Box-folder 484: 12)
    - Mohammed Reza Pahlavi, Shah of Iran (Box-folder 484: 13)
    - Moore, John R. (Box-folder 484: 14)
    - Morgenthau, Robert M. (Box-folder 484: 15)
    - Mosk, Stanley (Box-folder 484: 16)
    - Munzer, Rudy (Box-folder 484: 17)
    - Muskie, Edmund (Box-folder 484: 18)
    - Myers, Jim (Box-folder 484: 19)
    - Nicolson, David (Box-folder 484: 20)
    - Nitze, Paul (Box-folder 484: 21)
    - Nixon, Richard (Box-folder 484: 22)
    - Norton, Eleanor Holmes (Box-folder 484: 23)
    - Olivarez, Graciela (Box-folder 484: 24)
    - O'Neill, Thomas P. (Box-folder 484: 25)
    - Ortega, Joseph (Box-folder 484: 26)
    - Owens, Hugh F. (Box-folder 484: 27)
    - Parkinson, Ariel (Box-folder 484: 28)
    - Parks, Harold W. (Box-folder 484: 29)
    - Peterson, Wayne (Box-folder 484: 30)
    - Pfeiffer, Ralph A. (Box-folder 484: 31)
    - Platten, Donald C. (Box-folder 484: 32)
    - Politzer, Jerome (Box-folder 484: 33)
    - Post, A. Alan (Box-folder 485: 1)
    - Quintanilla, Maria Aline Griffith y Dexter, Condesa de (Box-folder 485: 2)
    - Ray, Robert D. (Box-folder 485: 3)
    - Reichmuth, Ben (Box-folder 485: 4)
    - Renner, John C. (Box-folder 485: 5)
    - Renouf, A. P. (Box-folder 485: 6)
    - Riles, Wilson C. (Box-folder 485: 7)
    - Robinson, James D. (Box-folder 485: 8)
    - Rockefeller, David (Box-folder 485: 9)
    - Rohatyn, Felix (Box-folder 485: 10)
    - Ruff, Howard (Box-folder 485: 11)
    - San Jose forum (Box-folder 485: 12)
    - Schultze, Charles (Box-folder 485: 13)
    - Seaborg, Glenn (Box-folder 485: 14)
    - Seeger, Charles (Box-folder 485: 15)
    - Shaklee, Forrest (Box-folder 485: 16)
    - Sharp, Ulysses S. Grant (Box-folder 485: 17)
    - Shaw, Spencer G. (Box-folder 485: 18)
    - Small, Robert (Box-folder 485: 19)
    - Snyder, Theodore (Box-folder 485: 20)
    - Sonenshein, R. Nathan (Box-folder 485: 21)
    - Stefanelli, Leonard (Box-folder 485: 22)
    - Stein, Herbert (Box-folder 485: 23)
    - Stockman, David (Box-folder 485: 24)
    - Streiker, Lowell (Box-folder 485: 25)
    - Stuhlmueller, Eric (Box-folder 485: 26)
    - Sutton, Antony (Box-folder 485: 27)
    - Taylor, Claude L. (Box-folder 485: 28)
    - Thatcher, Margaret (Box-folder 485: 29)
    - Time magazine list of 50 new leaders (Box-folder 485: 30)
    - Tolbert, William R. (Box-folder 485: 31)
    - Trucking deregulation debate (Box-folder 485: 32)
    - Tung, S. T. (Box-folder 485: 33)
    - Tyrrell, R. Emmett (Box-folder 485: 34)
    - Uhler, Lewis (Box-folder 485: 35)
    - Van Cleave, William (Box-folder 485: 36)
    - Van der Ryn, Sim (Box-folder 485: 37)
    - Viguerie, Richard A. (Box-folder 485: 38)
    - Visser, J. André (Box-folder 485: 39)
    - Wakeman, Howard (Box-folder 485: 40)
    - Ward, Douglas (Box-folder 486: 1)
    - Weil, Lorne (Box-folder 486: 2)
    - Welch, Jasper A. (Box-folder 486: 3)
    - Welch, John F. (Box-folder 486: 4)
    - Westmoreland, William C. (Box-folder 486: 5)
    - Young, Andrew (Box-folder 486: 6)
    - Zamzow, Dale (Box-folder 486: 7)
  - 1980
    - Alhegelan, Sheikh Faisal (Box-folder 486: 8)
    - Anderson, John B. (Box-folder 486: 9)
    - Arnold, Anthony (Box-folder 486: 10)
    - Baeder, Donald (Box-folder 486: 11)
    - Bentsen, Lloyd (Box-folder 486: 12)
    - Bertram, Christoph (Box-folder 486: 13)
    - Biaggini, Benjamin F. (Box-folder 486: 14)
    - Boggs, Hale (Box-folder 486: 15)
    - Boskin, Michael (Box-folder 486: 16)
    - Brown, Edmund G. (Box-folder 486: 17)
    - Brown, Harold (Box-folder 486: 18)
    - Burger, Warren E. (Box-folder 486: 19)
    - Bush, George H. W. (Box-folder 486: 20)
    - Business Week panel (Box-folder 486: 21)
    - Caradon, Lord (Box-folder 486: 22)
    - Chai, Zemin (Box-folder 486: 23)
    - Claybrook, Joan (Box-folder 486: 24)
    - Cousins, Norman (Box-folder 486: 25)
    - Cranston, Alan (Box-folder 487: 1)
    - Deukmejian, George (Box-folder 487: 2)
    - Djerassi, Carl (Box-folder 487: 3)
    - Duffy, Joseph D. (Box-folder 487: 4)
    - Duignan, Peter, and Alvin Rabushka (Box-folder 487: 5)
    - Duncan, Charles W. (Box-folder 487: 6)
    - Ellis, Richard (Box-folder 487: 7)
    - Ellisberg, Daniel (Box-folder 487: 8)
    - Emmerson, John K. (Box-folder 487: 9)
    - Field, Mervin D. (Box-folder 487: 10)
    - Fraser, Douglas A. (Box-folder 487: 11)
    - Friedman, Milton (Box-folder 487: 12)
    - Gann, Paul (Box-folder 487: 13)
    - Ghandour, Ali (Box-folder 487: 14)
    - Goldschmidt, Neil E. (Box-folder 487: 15)
    - Graham, Fred (Box-folder 487: 16)
    - Hamm, William G. (Box-folder 487: 17)
    - Hardy, H.W. (Box-folder 487: 18)
    - Harriman, Averell (Box-folder 487: 19)
    - Hartley, Fred L. (Box-folder 487: 20)
    - Hoadley, Walter A. (Box-folder 487: 21)
    - Holiday concert (Box-folder 487: 22)
    - Hufstedler, Shirley (Box-folder 487: 23)
    - Jamis, Jay (Box-folder 487: 24)
    - Jarvis, Howard (Box-folder 488: 1)
    - Jewett, Fritz (Box-folder 488: 2)
    - Johnson, Bruce M. (Box-folder 488: 3)
    - Kemeny, John G. (Box-folder 488: 4)
    - Kennedy, Donald (Box-folder 488: 5)
    - Kingman, Brewster (Box-folder 488: 6)
    - Kline, Anthony J. (Box-folder 488: 7)
    - Linowitz, Sol M. (Box-folder 488: 8)
    - Lucey, Patrick (Box-folder 488: 9)
    - Marcos, Imelda (Box-folder 488: 10)
    - Mark, Hans M. (Box-folder 488: 11)
    - McCarter, Neely (Box-folder 488: 12)
    - McCarthy, Leo T. (Box-folder 488: 13)
    - McGee, Vincent (Box-folder 488: 14)
    - McHenry, Donald F. (Box-folder 488: 15)
    - Mitgang, Iris (Box-folder 488: 16)
    - Mondale, Walter (Box-folder 488: 17)
    - Muskie, Edmund S. (Box-folder 488: 18)
    - Norris, Merwyn (Box-folder 488: 19)
    - Palmieri, Victor (Box-folder 488: 20)
    - Reagan, Ronald (Box-folder 488: 21)
    - Rohatyn, Felix (Box-folder 488: 22)
    - Sakharov, Vladimir (Box-folder 488: 23)
    - Saxon, David S. (Box-folder 489: 1)
    - Schultz, Frederick (Box-folder 489: 2)
    - Secord, Richard V. (Box-folder 489: 3)
    - Shaughnessy, Daniel (Box-folder 489: 4)
    - Slay, Alton (Box-folder 489: 5)
    - Smith, Geoffrey (Box-folder 489: 6)
    - Swearingen, John (Box-folder 489: 7)
    - Taylor, Kenneth D. (Box-folder 489: 8)
    - Teller, Edward (Box-folder 489: 9)
    - Themido, Joo Hall (Box-folder 489: 10)
    - Toffler, Alvin (Box-folder 489: 11)
    - Trudeau, Pierre (Box-folder 489: 12)
    - Tzounis, John (Box-folder 489: 13)
    - Unification Church (Box-folder 489: 14)
    - Verity, William C. (Box-folder 489: 15)
    - Wahed, Joseph (Box-folder 489: 16)
    - Williams, Harold (Box-folder 489: 17)
    - Woodcock, Leonard (Box-folder 489: 18)
    - Zinner, Paul (Box-folder 489: 19)
  - 1981
    - American Relief Administration executives (Box-folder 489: 20)
    - Amoss, W. J. (Box-folder 489: 21)
    - Anderson, John B. (Box-folder 489: 22)
    - Armacost, Samuel (Box-folder 489: 23)
    - Baez, Joan (Box-folder 489: 24)
    - Batten, William M. (Box-folder 489: 25)
    - Beach, Morrison H. (Box-folder 489: 26)
    - Bennett, William R. (Box-folder 490: 1)
    - Berg, Paul (Box-folder 490: 2)
    - Blum, Yehuda (Box-folder 490: 3)
    - Bookout, John F. (Box-folder 490: 4)
    - Bradley, Thomas (Box-folder 490: 5)
    - Braman, Norman, and Alan C. Nelson (Box-folder 490: 6)
    - Brause, Alberto, and candidates for officers (Box-folder 490: 7)
    - Britton, Herchell (Box-folder 490: 8)
    - Broder, David S. (Box-folder 490: 9)
    - Brown, Willie L. (Box-folder 490: 10)
    - Bryson, John E. (Box-folder 490: 11)
    - Bush, George H. W. (Box-folder 490: 12)
    - Butler, Adam (Box-folder 490: 13)
    - Campbell, William (Box-folder 490: 14)
    - Carlucci, Frank (Box-folder 490: 15)
    - Carter, Harlon B. (Box-folder 490: 16)
    - Casper, Andrew (Box-folder 490: 17)
    - Clark, Ed (Box-folder 490: 18)
    - Clifford, Robert (Box-folder 490: 19)
    - Conger, Harry M. (Box-folder 490: 20)
    - Cooney, David M. (Box-folder 490: 21)
    - Cory, Kenneth (Box-folder 490: 22)
    - Coughlin, Bernard J. (Box-folder 490: 23)
    - Cox, Archibald (Box-folder 490: 24)
    - Crane, Philip M. (Box-folder 490: 25)
    - Cunningham, Mary (Box-folder 490: 26)
    - Davis, John R. (Box-folder 491: 1)
    - Dayton, Kenneth N. (Box-folder 491: 2)
    - Debolt, Dorothy and Robert (Box-folder 491: 3)
    - Deukmejian, George (Box-folder 491: 4)
    - Donahue, Phil (Box-folder 491: 5)
    - Dreyfus, Lee Sherman (Box-folder 491: 6)
    - Duignan, Peter J. (Box-folder 491: 7)
    - Durst, Mose (Box-folder 491: 8)
    - Dwight, Herbert (Box-folder 491: 9)
    - Elekdag, Sakru (Box-folder 491: 10)
    - Falwell, Jerry (Box-folder 491: 11)
    - Felix, John H. (Box-folder 491: 12)
    - Ford, Gerald (Box-folder 491: 13)
    - Fraknoi, Andrew (Box-folder 491: 14)
    - Francis, Amadeo I. D. (Box-folder 491: 15)
    - Freeman, Roger (Box-folder 491: 16)
    - Friendly, Fred (Box-folder 491: 17)
    - Gibson, Andrew (Box-folder 491: 18)
    - Gilmour, Ian (Box-folder 491: 19)
    - Granville, Joseph E. (Box-folder 491: 20)
    - Gutman, Peter (Box-folder 491: 21)
    - Habib, Philip C. (Box-folder 491: 22)
    - Hackett, David (Box-folder 491: 23)
    - Hahn, Bradley (Box-folder 491: 24)
    - Haig, Alexander (Box-folder 491: 25)
    - Hamilton, Wilbur (Box-folder 491: 26)
    - Hanley, John W. (Box-folder 491: 27)
    - Harman, Willis (Box-folder 491: 28)
    - Harper, Ed (Box-folder 491: 29)
    - Harty, Sheila (Box-folder 491: 30)
    - Hoadley, Walter E. (Box-folder 491: 31)
    - Holzach, Robert (Box-folder 491: 32)
    - Honig, Bill (Box-folder 491: 33)
    - Huang, Hua (Box-folder 492: 1)
    - Hufstedler, Seth (Box-folder 492: 2)
    - Inauguration and concert (Box-folder 492: 3)
    - Jervis, John (Box-folder 492: 4)
    - Johnson, Alexandra (Box-folder 492: 5)
    - Kanaga, William S. (Box-folder 492: 6)
    - Keller, George (Box-folder 492: 7)
    - Kendall, Donald M. (Box-folder 492: 8)
    - Kennan, George (Box-folder 492: 9)
    - Kennedy, Moorhead (Box-folder 492: 10)
    - Laingen, Bruce R. (Box-folder 492: 11)
    - Larosire, Jacques de (Box-folder 492: 12)
    - Lehrman, Lewis (Box-folder 492: 13)
    - Love, Ruth B. (Box-folder 492: 14)
    - Manatt, Charles (Box-folder 492: 15)
    - Meese, Edwin (Box-folder 492: 16)
    - Nelson, Gaylord (Box-folder 492: 17)
    - Neumann, Robert G. (Box-folder 492: 18)
    - Newsweek panel (Box-folder 492: 19)
    - Okawara, Yoshio (Box-folder 492: 20)
    - O'Malley, Desmond (Box-folder 492: 21)
    - Parry, Robert (Box-folder 492: 22)
    - Perkins, Thomas J. (Box-folder 492: 23)
    - Raven, Robert D. (Box-folder 492: 24)
    - Reagan, Maureen (Box-folder 492: 25)
    - Riles, Wilson (Box-folder 492: 26)
    - Rivlin, Alice M. (Box-folder 492: 27)
    - Ruppe, Loret Miller (Box-folder 492: 28)
    - Seibert, Donald V. (Box-folder 492: 29)
    - Servan-Schreiber, Jean-Jacques (Box-folder 492: 30)
    - Shabtai, Sabi H. (Box-folder 492: 31)
    - Shields, Nelson T. (Box-folder 492: 32)
    - Smith, Roger B. (Box-folder 492: 33)
    - Sowell, Thomas (Box-folder 492: 34)
    - Sterling, Claire (Box-folder 492: 35)
    - Strauss, Simon D. (Box-folder 493: 1)
    - Vogel, Hans-Jochen (Box-folder 493: 2)
    - Watkins, James R. (Box-folder 493: 3)
    - Webster, William H. (Box-folder 493: 4)
    - Weinberger, Caspar W. (Box-folder 493: 5)
    - Wilson, Pete (Box-folder 493: 6)
    - Yankelevich, Tanya (Box-folder 493: 7)
    - Young, John, and Robert Crippen (Box-folder 493: 8)
  - 1982
    - Agee, William M. (Box-folder 493: 9)
    - Amaya, Naohiro (Box-folder 493: 10)
    - Amit, Daniel (Box-folder 493: 11)
    - Anderson, Robert O. (Box-folder 493: 12)
    - Asner, Ed (Box-folder 493: 13)
    - Beggs, James M. (Box-folder 493: 14)
    - Bradley, Tom (Box-folder 493: 15)
    - Brown, Edmund G. (Box-folder 493: 16)
    - Brown, Edmund G., and Pete Wilson debate (Box-folder 493: 17)
    - Buckley, James L. (Box-folder 493: 18)
    - Business Week panel (Box-folder 493: 19)
    - Butcher, Willard C. (Box-folder 493: 20)
    - Campbell, Wallace (Box-folder 493: 21)
    - Carlson, Richard C. (Box-folder 494: 1)
    - Casey, William J. (Box-folder 494: 2)
    - Commoner, Barry (Box-folder 494: 3)
    - Deukmejian, George (Box-folder 494: 4)
    - Draper, William H. (Box-folder 494: 5)
    - Drinan, Robert F. (Box-folder 494: 6)
    - Enders, Thomas O. (Box-folder 494: 7)
    - Erdman, Paul (Box-folder 494: 8)
    - Fery, John B. (Box-folder 494: 9)
    - Gavin, John (Box-folder 494: 10)
    - Gephardt, Richard A. (Box-folder 494: 11)
    - Gorsuch, Anne M. (Box-folder 494: 12)
    - Gotlieb, Allan E. (Box-folder 494: 13)
    - Hassan bin Talal, Prince of Jordan (Box-folder 494: 14)
    - Heyman, Ira (Box-folder 494: 15)
    - Hill, Alan A. (Box-folder 494: 16)
    - Hoadley, Walter E. (Box-folder 494: 17)
    - Inauguration and concert (Box-folder 494: 18)
    - Joseph, James A. (Box-folder 494: 19)
    - Kirkpatrick, Jeane (Box-folder 494: 20)
    - Lapidus, Ira (Box-folder 494: 21)
    - Lewis, Drew (Box-folder 495: 1)
    - McCaffrey, Stanley E. (Box-folder 495: 2)
    - McCloskey, Pete (Box-folder 495: 3)
    - McEwen, Terrence (Box-folder 495: 4)
    - McGovern, George (Box-folder 495: 5)
    - MacGregor, Ian (Box-folder 495: 6)
    - Martin, Philip (Box-folder 495: 7)
    - Maynard, Robert C. (Box-folder 495: 8)
    - Mielke, Frederick W. (Box-folder 495: 9)
    - Mondale, Walter (Box-folder 495: 10)
    - Mosk, Stanley (Box-folder 495: 11)
    - Neuharth, Allen H. (Box-folder 495: 12)
    - Peripheral Canal debate (Box-folder 495: 13)
    - Peterson, Russel (Box-folder 495: 14)
    - Pierce, Samuel (Box-folder 495: 15)
    - Quinn, John R. (Box-folder 495: 16)
    - Ramin, David (Box-folder 495: 17)
    - Republican presidential candidates (Box-folder 495: 18)
    - Richards, Richard (Box-folder 495: 19)
    - Riding, Alan (Box-folder 495: 20)
    - Roberts, John (Box-folder 495: 21)
    - Robinson, Jim (Box-folder 496: 1)
    - Roderick, David M. (Box-folder 496: 2)
    - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano, Jr. (Box-folder 496: 3)
    - Said, Edward W. (Box-folder 496: 4)
    - Seaborg, Glenn T. (Box-folder 496: 5)
    - Shoven, John (Box-folder 496: 6)
    - Smith, William French (Box-folder 496: 7)
    - Stockdale, James (Box-folder 496: 8)
    - Talbot, Frank Hamilton (Box-folder 496: 9)
    - Voinovich, George (Box-folder 496: 10)
    - Watanabe, Michio (Box-folder 496: 11)
    - Whitman, Marina von Neumann (Box-folder 496: 12)
    - Williams, Samuel L. (Box-folder 496: 13)
    - Wilson, Pete (Box-folder 496: 14)
    - Wright, Oliver (Box-folder 496: 15)
    - Zia-ul-Haq, Mohammad (Box-folder 496: 16)
    - Zinner, Paul E. (Box-folder 496: 17)
  - 1983
    - Abourezk, James (Box-folder 496: 18)
    - Adler, Mortimer (Box-folder 496: 19)
    - Armstrong, James (Box-folder 496: 20)
    - Asencio, Diego (Box-folder 496: 21)
    - Baker, James A. (Box-folder 497: 1)
    - Baldridge, Malcolm (Box-folder 497: 2)
    - Baxter, William F. (Box-folder 497: 3)
    - Beichman, Arnold (Box-folder 497: 4)
    - Bennett, William J. (Box-folder 497: 5)
    - Bookbinder, Hyman (Box-folder 497: 6)
    - Brock, William E. (Box-folder 497: 7)
    - Brown, John Y. (Box-folder 497: 8)
    - Brzezinski, Zbigniew (Box-folder 497: 9)
    - Butterfield, Fox (Box-folder 497: 10)
    - Crutcher, John W. (Box-folder 497: 11)
    - Dellums, Ronald (Box-folder 497: 12)
    - Deukmejian, George (Box-folder 497: 13)
    - Dole, Robert (Box-folder 497: 14)
    - Erb, Richard (Box-folder 497: 15)
    - Erdman, Paul (Box-folder 497: 16)
    - Feldstein, Martin (Box-folder 497: 17)
    - Friedman, Milton (Box-folder 497: 18)
    - Friedman, Philip J. (Box-folder 497: 19)
    - Fuller, Mary Falvey (Box-folder 497: 20)
    - Gibbons, John C. (Box-folder 497: 21)
    - Glenn, John (Box-folder 498: 1)
    - Hartman, Arthur Adair (Box-folder 498: 2)
    - Hawk, David (Box-folder 498: 3)
    - Hegner, Anton R. (Box-folder 498: 4)
    - Hoadley, Walter E. (Box-folder 498: 5)
    - Hodel, Donald P. (Box-folder 498: 6)
    - Hodsoll, Frank (Box-folder 498: 7)
    - Honig, Bill (Box-folder 498: 8)
    - Koch, Ed (Box-folder 498: 9)
    - Lighthizer, Robert (Box-folder 498: 10)
    - Linowitz, Myron (Box-folder 498: 11)
    - Lougheed, Peter (Box-folder 498: 12)
    - McCloskey, Paul N. (Box-folder 498: 13)
    - McGowan, William (Box-folder 498: 14)
    - Miller, James C. (Box-folder 498: 15)
    - Mousalam, Barbara (Box-folder 498: 16-17)
    - Narayanan, K. R. (Box-folder 498: 18)
    - Orfila, Alejandro (Box-folder 498: 19)
    - Pastora, Eden (Box-folder 498: 20)
    - Paterno, Joe (Box-folder 498: 21)
    - Peters, Thomas J. (Box-folder 498: 22)
    - Peterson, Peter G. (Box-folder 498: 23)
    - Phelan, John J. (Box-folder 499: 1)
    - Prawy, Marcel (Box-folder 499: 2)
    - Premadasa, Ranasinghe (Box-folder 499: 3)
    - Prussia, Leland S. (Box-folder 499: 4)
    - Reagan, Ronald (Box-folder 499: 5)
    - Riesman, David (Box-folder 499: 6)
    - Rostropovich, Mstislav (Box-folder 499: 7)
    - Rule, Elton H. (Box-folder 499: 8)
    - Salinger, Pierre (Box-folder 499: 9)
    - Salisbury, Harrison E. (Box-folder 499: 10)
    - Schwab, Charles (Box-folder 499: 11)
    - Sellars, Gerard L. (Box-folder 499: 12)
    - Shanker, Albert (Box-folder 499: 13)
    - Sills, Beverly (Box-folder 499: 14)
    - Sullivan, Leon H. (Box-folder 499: 15)
    - Turner, Stansfield (Box-folder 499: 16)
    - Vernier-Palliez, Bernard (Box-folder 499: 17)
    - Wenjin, Zhang (Box-folder 499: 18)
    - White House Fellows (Box-folder 499: 19)
    - Winpisinger, William (Box-folder 499: 20)
    - Wilson, John (Box-folder 499: 21)
    - Wilson, Margaret Bush (Box-folder 499: 22)
    - Zabih, Seper (Box-folder 499: 23)
    - Zschau, Ed (Box-folder 499: 24)
  - 1984
    - Alvarez, Luis W. (Box-folder 500: 1)
    - Arens, Moshe (Box-folder 500: 2)
    - Bajpai, Kayatani Shankar (Box-folder 500: 3)
    - Bennack, Frank A. (Box-folder 500: 4)
    - Bennet, Douglas J. (Box-folder 500: 5)
    - Bevan, Timothy (Box-folder 500: 6)
    - Borchgrave, Arnaud de (Box-folder 500: 7)
    - Bouhabib, Abdallah Rashid (Box-folder 500: 8)
    - Breslauer, George W. (Box-folder 500: 9)
    - Bunzel, John (Box-folder 500: 10)
    - Bush, George H. W. (Box-folder 500: 11)
    - Business Week panel (Box-folder 500: 12)
    - Cape, Ron (Box-folder 500: 13)
    - Cappiello, Frank A. (Box-folder 500: 14)
    - Casey, William J. (Box-folder 500: 15)
    - Chavez, Sazarv (Box-folder 500: 16)
    - Clark, William P. (Box-folder 500: 17)
    - Cranston, Alan (Box-folder 501: 1)
    - Crowe, William J. (Box-folder 501: 2)
    - Dam, Kenneth W. (Box-folder 501: 3)
    - Dole, Elizabeth (Box-folder 501: 4)
    - Drury, Alan (Box-folder 501: 5)
    - Egger, Roscoe (Box-folder 501: 6)
    - Ehrlich, Paul (Box-folder 501: 7)
    - Erdman, Paul (Box-folder 501: 8)
    - Evert-Lloyd, Chris (Box-folder 501: 9)
    - Fairbanks, Richard M. (Box-folder 501: 10)
    - Falwell, Jerry (Box-folder 501: 11)
    - Field, Mervin (Box-folder 501: 12)
    - Friedman, Milton (Box-folder 501: 13)
    - Gaines, Ernest J. (Box-folder 501: 14)
    - Gardner, David (Box-folder 501: 15)
    - Gelb, Leslie (Box-folder 501: 16)
    - Goldwater, Barry (Box-folder 501: 17)
    - Graham, Daniel (Box-folder 501: 18)
    - Guinn, Donald E. (Box-folder 501: 19)
    - Hambrecht, William (Box-folder 502: 1)
    - Hoadley, Walter E. (Box-folder 502: 2)
    - Holiday concert (Box-folder 502: 3)